Luv kids we are gathered here today to
talk about something that day there was
no problem with him and as soon as he somehow
controlled himself the child fell down
his Rajesh brought him and
now father rushed him to the hospital when they
reached the hospital they said that he has a
head injury and it will take a long time for him to recover
and it is
likely that by the grace of God everything is fine the
boy who saved the flashlight was riding a very fast
bike and he
could have gone and pulled the child so hard if the child had worn a helmet then
perhaps the children would not have been hurt as much as
they were and the recovery time would have been less so so
come on today we want to appoint someone here
who decides that we can save children from accidents in the future
and as you have been told
because of this we cannot subscribe by
subscribing we are able to reach you a
little bit in the form of this video the
full opportunity is in our hearts no no
let's start how we can
save each other in this way we can
save others from getting hurt  Because ours so
let's see that in this entire video
we will talk about those people
we will talk about riders
we will talk about people you
like this dream number every day on the road there are
road accidents in hours water drips
[music]
number 2424 and then 24365 you get this
dream your akhya akhya two-wheeler
people number about one lakh 1 lakh
13 thousand and subscribe and 2018 this is the
truth here we have charts in India and the whole world
that every day the fat that increases is from husband
to zinc and the
number of people subscribing to this channel if you look
at the whole world then that is 10 and the
number of people getting injured if you look at the
people of the world also increases by the hour
people get injured in the world it is
just that we have nothing new
so first of all we have to follow the rules of
brushing our teeth not
eating just like that now we
love our father very much this is also that
we keep you safe if you get sick
Whatever the reason is,
you also have to take care of them in the same way.
What will you do if you are going out somewhere?
Both mom and dad love each other.
[Music] Do it.
This flood water in the sea
remains in the entire country.
Around 230,000 people lose their lives due to tsunamis in the sea all over the world
and the total number of people in the whole world is
known to us and
we have 90% subscribers in 2018 and half the people in 2016.
Now we will see that in the recent times,
this does not happen according to the family members. If someone gets
injured, it takes a lot of time to go to the
hospital. You get medicines on time
and this is a huge amount of money. Every year, this is for the
security of our country.
And our population in this
country is so huge that it is very shocking.
Why are the mothers of children below the age of 19
not with their children?
Every minute, a child loses
his life in a road accident.
What do we have to do? You
can reduce this number. This is a picture of this.
In the picture you will see that if you stop one then it will
create danger for me, in the same way
you will see here that there are some boys
who cross the road over the divider,
we and you should think that
you might get angry, to save you there is
only our safety here and there, the
possibility of two children increases and the
children will feel
a big problem, then here you
see that you are a boy, you are riding this bike, then the
children go out and you
hit him with your bike,
due to which this is not right,
yes brother now we see that our traffic
system is especially for those who are saying
that they should never subscribe and like in the middle of standing bushes, so that
you do not have any nightmare, so in the same
way you should walk or not, come, nothing
and roasting some things board is
absolutely Amrit children, road road and this is not the
other one is ready to cancel the vehicles coming and going, is
it understandable if you
mean it then subscribe us here,
if there is a
slide show there,
why don't we talk about some symptoms of that, that
you too in homes or  I will meet you again
always why are you standing there that due to the
increasing number of accidents and deaths, do
not go home and for those who are
not affected by the speed limit,
then you can have 4 GB on WhatsApp but you have to keep in
mind that their situation is also in your hands, if you are
always turning on the vehicle,
you have to use the signal, there is up to
one seat between two players, if you
want to see the vehicle giving information, then wait for a
long time near the back street, for that,
follow the traffic rules in all the cars, bikes, scooters and this picture,
in the picture, four-five people, so many people
automatically, Michael,
let's go here, if it gets away from your house, the
chances of it increase, so that we make it clear
that our
excellent people are those who are not even
hit by the vehicles between them, you do
not get angry,
well, skin platform long liver
transplant can be done, we can change everything, we cannot
change the thing, he will
leave us because of this change, no one
knows that due to injury, it can be prevented, the tendency to
forget you can be done  There
may be a problem at home, do one thing, subscribe, you can also learn to
improve your power of thinking and understanding, this can be a lesson for China, how
can you protect yourself, it is
definitely for your children too, the tree is
available, it is available in the market,
in this program made for children, we will tell you from
here, okay,
definitely,
helmets are made for children, small helmets and
this thing protects your head from
any kind of injury, children should cover themselves with crackers,
subscribe, no, the
chances increase, like right now, it is
not necessary to
talk to people from a distance, if you are coming home from outside, then you should
keep it so that we can
protect ourselves, similarly, from the month of March,
this is only two,
now see, I told you that this year it
reduces the possibility of fog,
it is saving you from cleaning it from inside to protect your body,
this is spread in front, you can see,
in the meantime, apply it now, how it
protects you from our roads, water, dust, dirt and sunlight and yes, it protects you from feeling hot, for this it is
important to keep it here  It is important that we must
wear this protective helmet, you must wear it
while buying all this subscribe and tell
that Nihal is one of the five sons who
wears this helmet for walking and playing, this is
white in colour, these helmets of allotment are
not worn for walking, their helmets are different, this
helmet of ours
is as per Bureau of Indian Standards,
first IS Commissioner and Bhairav ​​Indian
Standard Times which IS A good Times
made motivational, these are
made on quality for you
that I was
robbed, I was robbed, I wore
helmet every time, you usually wear it
for your safety, let's
see MP4 video,
scientists have robbed a helmet in a college, scientists have done a helmet, let's
see some more signs of
how we are, family to family, that
family where people go out wearing hair packs,
when you are a family, it is always there and after this,
as we will talk about helping each other if someone gets
robbed, the video and
once broken, both the numbers are very important and
keep this thing in mind that according to them,
police will not bother you if you
need someone to go to hospital or road  We help in case of accidents
here by giving the correct information to the police
first so that if
you want you can do everything and whoever does
not bother you is
yours, if someone is asked that the
body becomes very hot due to great pleasure then there is
no water at all if you do it then if the
temperature of the patient will go up and if not then
he is getting hurt and the same doctor and if
you have not subscribed you know that
from both the sides
I will then slowly insert you and slowly take it
out for a minute, half the color is black and take it out
as per the busyness, he is
positioned in the same position, if
people die in road accidents then it happens to us, with the
help of which the body slowly goes
down and we do not even know, so a
very good way for that is to
make a position of him in such a way that his
breathing process will continue,
how do you take the first photo, take the second photo
like this, second one like this
and in whichever way she is facing, in the
same way in the photo the girl is
kept in such a way that
you will turn her over like this
now I am  If something is attached to you, it is very easy, the
main host will come out and it
will open with it and we can tie a rope or cloth from above around that person so that you
come in each other's arms,
if your leg is hurt, you can see here, if your leg is
hurt, then
tie it here, if there is an injury here, then
tie it here and if you show the file, then
wear it so that the blood flow can be stopped, a
small thing, we will come again, some tips, you should
remember this, whatever you have to
wear, if you are not just a driver, if you are not a swimmer, then
first of all he should always use the
signal while turning the car, he should
definitely use the voice commands, do not
go above that, I will be in the right place, if you do
not have any and these small things, it
means that you cannot do this, this will
not make you hungry for two quick times, different things and
all these will add water, take
less, that is, a
specific, brainless thing, if you are
sitting with someone, you will take some pride in yourself, we have taken
training here
that we will bring this in the morning, just keep it and keep playing, keep
watching your hands  Maintain question status
Thank you